eguyz.com 2009-01-29

# E! Guyz - Privacy Policy

eGuyz respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use eGuyz's services ("eGuyz Services"). Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission or as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). 

### eGuyz and Cookies

Upon your first visit to eGuyz.com, eGuyz sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. eGuyz uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. eGuyz does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people use the eGuyz Services. eGuyz will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the eGuyz Services may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

### What Information Do We Collect?

eGuyz does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. For example, eGuyz DOES collect such information from those users registering as Community Users and/or User Editors. eGuyz notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. For example, eGuyz may use your IP address or browser language to determine which language to use when showing search results or advertisements. 

### Links to Other Sites 

The stories/sites displayed and/or linked to by the eGuyz.com Service are developed by people over whom eGuyz exercises no control. Other links are also on sites not controlled by eGuyz. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. eGuyz encourages you to read the privacy policy of all web sites you visit. eGuyz may choose to exhibit its results in the form of a "URL redirecter." When eGuyz uses a URL redirecter, if you click on a URL on a eGuyz page, information about the click is sent to eGuyz, and eGuyz in turn sends you to the site you clicked on. eGuyz uses this URL information to understand and improve the quality of eGuyz's technology.

### With Whom Does eGuyz Share Information?

eGuyz may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average eGuyz user visits eGuyz, or which eGuyz pages are most often used. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. Further, eGuyz reserves the right to cooperate with legitimate law enforcement requests for information at its sole discretion.

### Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.  If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

### Third Party Advertising

eGuyz uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

### Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy

By using the eGuyz Services and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. eGuyz may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

### Who can I ask if I have additional questions?

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. [Contact us](http://www.eguyz.com/forums/sendmessage.php).
